Guide to the Yale Diploma Collection
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Inventory, Accession 19ND-A-400
  - David Brewer, BA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - William Aldrich Bushee, BA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - Edward Chester, BA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - Edward Orson Cowles, BA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - Andrew Cheves Dulles, MA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - Charles Edward Fellowes, BA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - Julius Gay, BA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - James Raymond Goodrich, MA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - Augustine Hart, MA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - Henry Cornelius Robinson, BA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - Samuel Brigham Spooner, MA, 1856 (Box 12)
  - John Griswold, BA, 1857 (Box 12)
  - John Worthington Hooker, MD, 1857 (Box 12)
  - John Chapin Sanders, MA, 1857 (Box 12)
  - Lewis Ledyard Weld, MA, 1847 (Box 12)
  - James Bird, MA, 1858 (Box 12)
  - Abner Colgate, BA, 1858 (Box 12)
  - Julius Gay, BA, 1858 (Box 12)
  - Luzon Burritt Morris, BA, 1858 (Box 12)
  - George Pratt, MA, 1858 (Box 12)
  - James Gardiner Vose, MA, 1858 (Box 12)
  - William Wheeler, MA, 1858 (Box 12)
  - David Josiah Brewer, MA, 1859 (Box 12)
  - William Henry Brewer, MA, 1859 (Box 12)
  - Benjamin Spencer Catlin, BA, 1859 (Box 12)
  - Julius Gay, MA, 1859 (Box 12)
  - William James Harris, MA, 1859 (Box 12)
  - Charlton Thomas Lewis, MA, 1859 (Box 12)
  - Thomas Bucklin Wells, BA, 1859 (Box 12)
  - Arthur Williams Wright, BA, 1859 (Box 12)
  - Whittlesey Adams, MA, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Daniel Cady Eaton, BA, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Nelson Gregory Hall, MD, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Edward Goodman Holden, BA, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - John Howard, BA, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Henry Strong Huntington, MA, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Joseph Cooke Jackson, MA, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Henry Martin Seely, MA, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Manning Case Wells, MA, 1860 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Frederic Stanton Davis, BA, 1861 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - John Coddington Kinney, BA, 1861 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - John Ellis Marshall, BA, 1851 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - David Judson Ogden, BA, 1861 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - George Clap Perkins, BA, 1861 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - James Pepper Pratt, BA, 1861 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - John Reuben Webster, BA, 1861 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - James Morris Whiton, PhD, 1861 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Arthur Williams Wright, BA [original and copy], 1861 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - William Aldrich Bushee, MA, 1862 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Benjamin Spencer Catlin, MA, 1862 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Benjamin Spencer Catlin, MD [sic], 1862 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Edward Orson Cowles, MD, 1862 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - James Mason Hoppin, MA, 1862 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Merritt Cicero Page, BA, 1862 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Samuel Parsons, Ph.B., 1862 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Theodore Runyon, MA, 1862 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Thomas Bucklin Wells, MA, 1862 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Cornelius Wade Bull, BA, 1863 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Jonathan Edwards, BA, 1863 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Thornton Mills Hinkle, BA, 1863 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - William Ingraham Kip, MA, 1863 (Box 13, Box 4)
  - Othniel Charles Marsh, MA, 1863 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Charles Hunter Owen, MA, 1863 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Harlan Page Parmelee, BA, 1863 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Charles Webster, BA, 1863 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Lewis Sendham Worthington, MA, 1863 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Thomas Boltwood, BA, 1864 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Robert Long Brownfield, Ph.B., 1864 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Robert Linton Chamberlain, MA, 1854 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Robert Shoemaker Ives, BA, 1864 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Bennett Warner Morse, MA, 1864 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Charles Green Rockwood, BA, 1864 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Gustavus J. Stoeckel, Doc. of Music [honorary], 1864 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Edward Royall Tyler, BA, 1864 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Arthur Van Harlingen, Ph.B., 1864 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - William Maxwell Evarts, LL.D., 1865 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - William Alexander Magill, MA, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - George Clay Perkins, MA, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Richard Salter Storrs, MA, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - John Shelly Weinberger, MA, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Peter Washington Wildey, MA, 1865 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - George Blagden Bacon, MA, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - John Taylor Baird, MA, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - William Binney, MA, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - George Brooks Curtiss, MA, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - William Whitman Farnam, BA, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Robert Shoemaker Ives, MD, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Joseph McKeehan McClure, BA, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - William Augustus Reynolds, MA, 1866 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Charles Greene Rockwood, Ph.D., 1866 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Cornelius Wade Bull, MD, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Charles Clemens Carpenter, MA, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Henry Martyn Colton, MA, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Robert Shoemaker Ives, MA, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - William Henry Morse, BA, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Roswell Parish, MA, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Charles Greene Rockwood, MA, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Oliver Sherman White, MA, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Edward Moore Williams, MA, 1867 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Enoch George Adams, MA, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - John Henry Granniss, MD, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - George Anson Jackson, Ph.B., 1868 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Luther Jones, MA, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Samuel Hopkins Riddell, MA, 1868 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Porter Cornelius Bliss, MA, 1869 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Augustus Jay DuBois, Ph.B., 1869 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - William Whitman Farnam, MA, 1869 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Albert Francis Hale, MA, 1869 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Edward Elbridge Salisbury, LL.D. [honorary], 1869 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Ernest Schroeder, MA, 1869 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Edward Salisbury Dana, BA, 1870 (Box 14)
  - Augustus Jay DuBois, C.E. [Civil Engineering - "Scientiae Machinatis Magistri"]
  - Henry Parker Fellows, BA, 1870 (Box 14)
  - Henry Ward Foote, MA, 1870 (Box 14)
  - Ira Emory Forbes, BA, 1870 (Box 14)
  - Simeon Thomas Hyde, MA, 1870 (Box 14)
  - Alfred Eugene Nolen, MA, 1870 (Box 14)
  - Thomas Day Seymour, BA [honorary], 1870 (Box 14)
  - Henry Farnham, MA, 1871 (Box 14)
  - Bentamin S. Richards, BA, 1871 (Box 14)
  - Joseph Earl Sheffield, MA, 1871 (Box 14)
  - Gustav Mozart Stoeckel, BA, 1871 (Box 14)
  - John Jay DuBois, MA, 1872 (Box 14)
  - Henry Franklin Hail, LL.B., 1842 (Box 14)
  - Benjamin Hoppin, BA, 1872 (Box 14)
  - John Coddington Kinney, MA, 1872 (Box 14)
  - Theodore Salisbury Woolsey, BA, 1872 (Box 14)
  - George William Young, MA, 1872 (Box 14)
  - George Theodore Bliss, BA, 1873 (Box 14)
  - Augustus Jay DuBois, Ph.D., 1873 (Box 14)
  - James Edward English, MA, 1873 (Box 14)
  - Charles Sheldon Hastings, Ph.D., 1873 (Box 14)
  - Robert Jaffray, Ph.B., 1873 (Box 14)
  - Ross Johnston, MA, 1873 (Box 14)
  - Edward Alexander Lawrence, MA, 1873 (Box 14)
  - William Henry Morse, MA, 1873 (Box 14)
  - Robert Williams, BA, 1873 (Box 14)
  - Edward Salisbury Dana, MA, 1874 (Box 14)
  - Gustav Mozart Stoeckel, 1874 (Box 14)
  - Samuel Rossiter Betts, BA, 1875[sic] (Box 14)
  - James Hazleton Cook, BA, 1875[sic] (Box 14)
  - James Hazleton Cook, LL.B., 1876 (Box 14)
  - Arthur Twining Hadley, BA, 1876 (Box 14)
  - Alfred Rust, BA, 1876 (Box 14)
  - Charles Palmer Sanford, BA, 1876 (Box 14)
  - Theodore Salisbury Woolsey, LL.B., 1876 (Box 14)
  - John Kimberly Beach, BA, 1877 (Box 14)
  - Ardon Legrand Judd, BA, 1877 (Box 14)
  - George Edward Langdon, BA, 1877 (Box 14)
  - Anthony Sander, Ph.D., 1877 (Box 14)
  - Allan Mason Thomas, Ph.B., 1877 (Box 14)
  - Samuel Wells Williams, MA, 1877 (Box 14)
  - Samuel Fessenden Clark, Ph.B., 1878 (Box 14)
  - Andrew Fay Currier, BA, 1878 (Box 14)
  - Charles Parsons, BA, 1878 (Box 14)
  - David Thomas Roberts, LL. B., 1878 (Box 14)
  - John Seymour, LL.B., 1878 (Box 14)
  - Edward Wells Southworth, LL.M., 1878 (Box 14)
  - John Kimberly Beach, LL.B., 1879 (Box 14)
  - William Whitney Hawkes, BA, MD, 1879 (Box 14)
  - Ardon Legrand Judd, LL.B., 1879 (Box 14)
  - Malcolm McIvor McKenzie, MA, 1879 (Box 14)
  - Charles Franklin Bliss, BA, 1880 (Box 14)
  - George Lafayette Camm, LL.B., 1880 (Box 14)
  - Andrew Fay Currier, MD
  - Philip Golden Bartlett, BA, 1881 (Box 14)
  - Russell Anson Bigelow, BA, 1881 (Box 14)
  - George Frederick Bosworth, Ph.B., 1881 (Box 14)
  - Walter Ray Bridgman, BA, 1881 (Box 14)
  - Norman Smith Latham, Ph.B., 1882[sic] (Box 14)
  - Charles Stillman, BA, 1882 (Box 14)
  - Sarah Foote - certificate of 3-year attendance, School of Fine Arts, 1883 (Box 14)
  - John Atwood Moore, BA, 1883 (Box 14)
  - Henry Hastings Strong, BA, 1883 (Box 14)
  - Deonard Mayhew Daggett, BA, 1884 (Box 14)
  - Professor Greuner, BA [typescript of diploma], 1884 (Box 14)
  - Samuel Brown Hawley, Ph.B., 1884 (Box 14)
  - Albert McClellan Mathewson, LL.B., 1884 (Box 14)
  - Oliver Thomas Osborn, MD, 1884 (Box 14)
  - William Williams, BA, 1884 (Box 14)
  - Hervey DeLoss Leland, BA, 1885 (Box 15)
  - George Thomas Linsley, BA, 1885 (Box 15)
  - Lewis Milton Schmidt, Ph.B., 1885 (Box 15)
  - Samuel Kimball Bremer, BA, 1886 (Box 15)
  - Franklin Woodbury Fisk, S.T.D., 1886 (Box 15)
  - James Samuels, BA, 1887 (Box 15)
  - Charles Alling Tuttle, Ph.B., 1888 (Box 15)
  - Jesse Levi Bright, S.T.B., 1890 (Box 15)
  - Wolcott Webster Ellsworth, 1890 (Box 15)
  - Charles Alling Tuttle, MD, 1890 (Box 15)
  - William H. Pelton, 1891 (Box 15)
  - Walter Ray Bridgman, MA, 1892 (Box 15)
  - Milored [sic] Cleora Jordan, attendance certificate - Y.F.A., 1897 (Box 15)
  - Louis E. Voorheis, B.A., 1897 (Box 15)
  - Charles Everett Farr - certificate of law course attendance and exam passing - slip only, 1898 (Box 15)
  - Junius Crawley Ayler, LL.B., 1899 (Box 15)
  - Oliver Thomas Osborne, 1899 (Box 15)
  - John Hampden Thomas, MA, 1899 (Box 15)
  - Maurice Phillip Gould, BA, 1900 (Box 15)
  - Paul Skeels Peirce, Ph.D., 1900 (Box 15)
  - William Henry White, Ph.B., 1900 (Box 15)
  - Herbert Wescott Fisher, LL.B., 1901 (Box 15)
  - John Frederick Haas, LL.M., 1901 (Box 15)
  - James Anderson Parker, BA, 1901 (Box 15)
  - Frank Sheridan Warmth, Ph.B., 1901 (Box 15)
  - Arthur Shaler Williams, BA, 1901 (Box 15)
  - John DeCoven Alsop, BA, 1902 (Box 15)
  - Hollon Augustine Farr, MA, 1902 (Box 15)
  - Arthur Garfield Harrison, LL.B., 1902 (Box 15)
  - Robert Kilburn Root, Ph.D., 1902 (Box 15)
  - Erwin Stanley, B. Phil., 1902 (Box 15)
  - William Henry Brewer, LL.D., 1903 (Box 15)
  - Theodore Salisbury Woolsey, M.For., 1903 (Box 15)
  - Arthur Henry Bartlett, Ph.D., 1904 (Box 15)
  - Hollon Augustine Farr, Ph.D., 1904 (Box 15)
  - Andrew Keogh, MA, 1904 (Box 15)
  - John Caspar Kittle, BA, 1904 (Box 15)
  - Willard Curtis Hyatt, BA, 1905 (Box 15)
  - Wallace Alvin Wilson, BA, 1905 (Box 15)
  - Edwin Rogers Embree, BA, 1905 (Box 15)
  - William Leroy Ulrich, Ph.B., 1906 (Box 15)
  - William Williams, MA, 1906 (Box 15)
  - Albert Jeffreys Evans, LL.B., 1907 (Box 15)
  - Henry Peter Hass, Ph.B., 1907 (Box 15)
  - Howard Phipps, BA, 1907 (Box 15)
  - John Martin VanHarlingen, Ph.B., 1907 (Box 15)
  - John Kimberly Beach, MA, 1908 (Box 15)
  - Howard Emerson Church, Ph.B., 1908 (Box 15)
  - Himon Evans, Ph.B., 1908 (Box 15)
  - George Lincoln Hendrickson, MA, 1908 (Box 15)
  - Davenport Hooker, BA, 1908 (Box 15)
  - Clayton Harwood Huckans, Ph.B., 1908 (Box 15)
  - Alexis Augustus Kelsey, Ph.B., 1908 (Box 15)
  - Theodore Thornton Munger, S.T.D., 1908 (Box 15)
  - Albert Jeffreys Evans, BA, 1909 (Box 15)
  - Davenport Hooker, MA, 1909 (Box 15)
  - William Abraham Kincaid, BA, 1909 (Box 15)
  - Robert Emmett Dickson, M. Forestry, 1910 (Box 16)
  - Sheppard Bliss Gordy, BS; Heintzleman, 1910 (Box 16)
  - Anna Harriet Pierce, Yale Fine Arts Attendance Certificate, 1910 (Box 16)
  - Douglas Tracy Smith, BA, 1910 (Box 16)
  - Charles Reynolds Brown, MA, 1911 (Box 16)
  - Raymond Thompson Hill, Ph.D., 1911 (Box 16)
  - David Richards, Ph.B., 1911 (Box 16)
  - Charles Seymour, Ph.D., 1911 (Box 16)
  - Wallace Wilson, Ph.D., 1911 (Box 16)
  - Francis L. Driscoll, B.A., 1912 (Box 16)
  - Francis Russell Graves, LL.B., 1912 (Box 16)
  - Davenport Hooker, Ph.D., 1912 (Box 16)
  - Henry Daggett Hooker, BA, 1912 (Box 16)
  - Charles Parsons, BA, 1912 (Box 16)
  - Henry Humphrey Parsons, MA, 1912 (Box 16)
  - J. Ruben Piranin, Ph.B., 1912 (Box 16)
  - Henry Daggett Hooker, MA, 1913 (Box 16)
  - Henry Humphrey Parsons, BA [sic], 1913 (Box 16)
  - Malcolm Rutherford Thorpe, BA, 1913 (Box 16)
  - Walter Kelsey Watts, Ph.B., 1913 (Box 16)
  - John Kimberly Beach, LL.D., 1914 (Box 16)
  - David Brewer Karrick, BA, 1914 (Box 16)
  - Mildred Cleora Jordan, B.F.A., 1914 (Box 16)
  - Henry Daggett Hooker, Ph.D., 1915 (Box 16)
  - Levi Huick (?erased partially), BA, 1915 (Box 16)
  - Anna Henriettal Pierce, B.F.A., 1916 (Box 16)
  - Malcolm Rutherford Thorpe, Ph.D., 1916 (Box 16)
  - Howard Pierce Sawyer, MD ["conferred at the front, July 4, 1918, Mobile Hospital 39") PHOTOSTAT (Box 16)
  - James Madison Braden, BA, 1919 (Box 16)
  - Thomas Wells Farnum, MA, 1919 (Box 16)
  - Sherwood Smith Eberth, Ph.B., 1920 (Box 16)
  - Francis Schlesinger, MA, 1920 (Box 16)
  - Beverly Douglas, MS, 1921 (Box 16)
  - Carl Gustaf Erickson, Ph.D., 1921 (Box 16)
  - Albert Puester, Ph.B., 1921 (Box 16)
  - Knight Preston Roddy, Business Administration Certificate, S.S.S., 1921 (Box 16)
  - Bryant Franklin Tolles, B.A., 1922 (Box 16)
  - John Stuart Gordon, 1923 (Box 16)
  - Chester B. Bowles, BS, 1924 (Box 16)
  - Vance Reid Dittman, BA, 1925 (Box 16)
  - Edward Stephen Harkness, MA, 1925 (Box 16)
  - Elizabeth Anne deBlasiis, certificate of Proficiency in the Theory of Music, 1926 (Box 16)
  - Robert Farquhar, Ph.B., 1926 (Box 16)
  - Vance Reid Dittman, L.L.B., 1927 (Box 16)
  - Charles Reynolds Brown, S.T.D., 1928 (Box 16)
  - Elizabeth Anne deBlasiis, B.Mus., 1928 (Box 16)
  - Charles Beecher Hogan, BA, 1928 (Box 16)
  - George Townsend Adee, MA, 1931 (Box 17)
  - Theodore Sizer, MA, 1931 (Box 17)
  - John Locke Vaill, BS, 1931 (Box 17)
  - Floyd Tomkins Reynolds, LL.B., 1932 (Box 17)
  - Charles Beecher Hogan, MA, 1933 (Box 17)
  - Henry Lawton Wade White, BA, 1933 (Box 17)
  - Charles Seymour, Jr., BA, 1935 (Box 17)
  - Robert Kilburn Root, D.Litt., 1937 (Box 17)
  - John Perry Miller, Honorary, 1950 (Box 17)
  - Incomplete Diplomas - no dates [dates in brackets, etc. from Catalog of Graduates of Yale University, 1924], 1950
    - Alexander T. Hawkins [BA 1826] (Box 17)
    - Thomas Hill, President of Harvard [honorary 1863] (Box 17)
    - Edward Pascal McKinney, BA [1861] (Box 17)
    - Allen Ferdinand Owen, BA [1839] (Box 17)
    - Andrew Reed, S.T.D. [1834] (Box 17)
    - Edward Isaac Sanford, BA [1847] (Box 17)
    - Orrin Chester White, MD [1847 honorary] (Box 17)
    - Thomas Wickes, BA "Intended for Master" [1834 BA] (Box 17)
- Diploma of Ezra Stiles, 1749; Accession 2001-A-057
  Conditions Governing Access
  The materials are open for research.
  - Diploma of Ezra Stiles, 1749 (Box 1)
    Scope and Contents
    Consists of the masters diploma of Ezra Stiles, who also received a BA from Yale College in 1746.
- Diplomas, 1832-1929; Accession 2004-A-148 (Box 1)
  No inventory available.
- Diploma of Reuben Booth, 1816; Accession 2019-A-0027
  - Diploma of Reuben Booth, 1816 (Box 1, Folder 1)